[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 24]
It was all because of me
and my Sun Spirit
that Luo Ge was injured so badly.
Is it really wrong for me
to stay by his side?
Come with me.
Things have changed a lot
these days.
You may not have noticed
that sunglow has been appearing in Xiyin Mountain
for several days.
Sunglow is an ominous sign.
♫The begonia is red, but every promise makes it more withered♫
They represent danger or suffering.
Since they appeared in Xiyin Mountain,
♫It blooms alone, but the wind and rain are more violent♫
it means that something bad
will happen to Luo Ge.
♫Plants are not human beings, and ruthless fruits are planted♫
Ge
is the only Immortal in Immortal Palace.
I don't want him
to be hurt again.
♫How can you forget the innocence and ignorance when we first met?♫
You should also understand
how painful Ge is now
because of your Sun Fragments.
♫The butterfly emerges from the chrysalis, but it is difficult to fly to the sky♫
Don't you feel sad
to see someone you love suffer because of you?
♫The butterfly's wings were broken, and the dream fell without a trace♫
♫Because of their greed for the warmth of fire, they lost each other♫
♫There is a period of youth, and he is waiting for the spring breeze in the coming year♫
Please
cut off his affection.
♫How many times do we have to reincarnate♫
I don't want to
♫Before we meet again in the next life?♫
be in his way.
♫Suffer all grief and long hate♫
♫Reversed right and wrong dreams♫
♫I exiled my thousand-year-old body♫
♫Waiting for the ashes to slowly burn in the heart♫
♫Wait until the end of life to see the begonia turn red again♫
♫How many times do we have to reincarnate♫
♫Before we meet again in the next life?♫
♫Suffer all grief and long hate♫
♫Reversed right and wrong dreams♫
♫I exiled my thousand-year-old body♫
One of you cares about all living beings,
while the other one disrupts the Three Realms.
You are no longer him.
♫Waiting for the ashes to slowly burn in the heart♫
If you don't believe me,
you can see it yourself.
I will kill you
♫Wait until the end of life to see the begonia turn red again♫
even if I will be devastated to death by the Moon Sword.
Fu,
where are you going?
Would you believe me
if I said something happened to my race?
What's your reason?
There is no reason.
It is the place where I grew up.
My brother and I will definitely feel it
if something happens there.
I see.
I can live for two hours without water,
but my people
will definitely die without water.
If something really happens,
they can't even escape.
Will you come back
after you leave?
As soon as I confirm that Demon Palace is fine,
I'll be right back.
This way.
It is
the seawater from our Xiyin Mountain,
which is connected to the sea of the human world.
If you become invisible in the water,
the people from Immortal Palace
won't see you.
However,
you must come back
before sunset.
What if I don't come back?
If you don't come back...
It seems
that I can't do anything to you.
But,
no matter what your choice is,
I will never regret
the decision I made.
Luo Ning,
thank you.
Fu,
we'll soon find out
if you're trustworthy or not.
I thought Liu Shao was seriously injured,
so
I allowed her to recuperate in Feiyuan House for a few days.
Ge,
your spiritual power has been severely damaged this time,
and it may hurt your spiritual root.
You should stop seeing her again.
Sometimes...
I know.
I won't see her again.
Haven't you found her yet?
It's sunny today.
Is it so difficult for you
to find her?
Master,
we will definitely sense her aura,
if she's still alive.
She must have died
and her body has been eaten by fish.
I won't believe that
she would die so easily.
If she really died,
there would definitely be demonic aura scattered around.
There's no way we can't find any clues.
I'm just afraid
that someone has already taken her out of Xiyin Mountain,
or used some kind of methods
to hide her aura.
Then... now...
Hurry up and send more people to find her.
Don't slack off.
Yes.
Brother,
did you hear me?
Yes.
Brother.
What's wrong with Liu Shao being here with you?
I don't understand
why they wouldn't let her see you.
Brother, don't you think
you've really come back to life
since she came to Xiyin Mountain?
So,
I haven't been alive
in the past thousand years, have I?
No.
Well...
Only when there are lights in your eyes
and a smile on your face,
are you really alive.
Brother,
hasn't your Wang Bell been given to Liu Shao?
Why did you take it back?
I really shouldn't take back
what has been given to others.
Give it to her for me.
No.
Go by yourself.
Are you going or not?
No.
Demon King?
Immortal.
I can give her this Wang Bell
for you.
This is the herbal tea from Xiyin Mountain Garden.
Wan Sui said that it is imbued with the aura of heaven and earth,
and drinking it can improve one's cultivation.
You left in a hurry that day.
Are you okay?
I've been worrying about you.
I'm fine.
Really.
What happened to your hand?
Nothing.
What's wrong?
Why
do you drink tea with your left hand?
That's because
when I was practicing
the imperial flute recently,
I always felt that my left hand was not flexible enough.
So Mr. Tai asked me to practice my left hand.
Do you
have any plans for the future?
Go home.
I miss my home
and my parents.
Don't worry.
This is Immortal's natal artifact
that he asked me to give you.
Since I have decided to leave,
I can't take it.
Do you still blame him?
No.
That's my own decision.
I just hope
he can be fine.
You can take this Wang Bell,
so that
he won't feel too guilty maybe.
And you can go find me at Demon Palace,
if you ever feel lonely in the future.
Speaking of
my Demon Palace,
there is still a lack of a Demon Queen.
He Na...
I...
Just kidding.
Anyway, remember
that you are not alone.
At least in Demon Palace,
you can always take me as a friend.
Brother.
I felt that something happened to our people,
and that made me very worried.
Now it seems that nothing happened.
After all, you're here.
Those little demons are nothing.
I knew you would be worried.
That's why I would go to Immortal Palace to see you
as soon as it was over,
to tell you not to worry.
I didn't expect you to come back.
The Dan Tangerine at the door just happened to grow fruit.
I knew you like it,
so I brought you a few.
It feels so good at home.
There was Luo Ge's Protection Spell
where you were trapped,
how did you escape?
If I really want to escape,
no spell can stop me.
I made an agreement with Immortal Palace
that I can take you home
after I recover the Four Demons.
That day will come soon.
Don't act rashly
to cause trouble anymore.
So if I say
I'm not going back to Immortal Palace,
will you send me back anyway?
Just eat those tangerines.
What happened to your hand?
The spiritual veins of your hand have been destroyed,
and the meridians have been broken.
How could it happen?
Could it be that eagle demon did it?
Impossible.
He should be much weaker than you.
I accidentally caused it.
It's okay, Fu.
Even if one of my hands is destroyed,
I can still bring you back.
I remember you like this too.
But every year,
you would leave the biggest and sweetest ones to me.
I'll do as you say if you want me to go bcak to Immortal Palace.
I'll deal with
the rest of these little demons.
I'll be sure to find out
who else was involved in hurting your arm.
Will he come back?
♫In the sea of clouds, I looked at the reflection of the moon in the water♫
Kill him!
♫I kept waiting and arched my palms into a circle♫
♫The reflection gradually reminded me of our first meeting♫
♫I can no longer tell the difference between wind and rain♫
♫Even if I get the volley sword♫
♫I can't forget you♫
♫Our destiny has been sealed long ago♫
♫I have no other choice♫
♫He said that responsibility and love are difficult to balance♫
♫He had no choice but to leave me♫
♫The past has passed, so do not linger♫
♫My love for you is still so strong♫
♫Too many intertwined oaths and lies♫
When you come back,
I will definitely teach you a lesson.
♫Have shattered my dreams♫
♫Who would like to take a broken willow branch, and watch the moon alone in the blue sky♫
♫Life is like a grain of sand♫
♫It burns the fire in my heart♫
♫I want to burn myself to hear you say that you have never changed♫
Demon King!
Don't kill me!
No!
♫Why have you been so far away from me every time♫
Fu, you liar!
Aren't you coming back?
♫For billions of years♫
♫Can I use your hands to warm up the world again?♫
♫A few hasty nights♫
If I don't come back,
♫Too many intertwined oaths and lies♫
are you going to smash that water energy?
♫Have shattered my dreams♫
No.
But I can't guarantee
♫Who would like to take a broken willow branch, and watch the moon alone in the blue sky♫
that I won't tear you apart
and feed the fish in my pond.
Even if you feed countless fish,
none of them
will be able to help you with your homework.
You seem
to be right.
But
you're still two hours late.
Tell me.
How do you want me to punish you?
Do whatever you want.
I won't fight back.
What?
Were you thinking of fighting back?
I wouldn't dare.
Here.
I brought you something good.
What happened to your hand?
It's fine
that you sneaked out.
But how could you fight
with others
and get hurt?
You are too weak.
It won't happen again.
I will definitely defeat them next time,
so that they don't have any chance to hurt me.
What are you talking about?
I'm telling you not to fight with others.
I am not asking you to compete with others.
Fine.
I won't.
Here.
Have some Dan Tangerines.
This Dan Tangerine tree
was planted
for me by my brother 900 years ago.
Half of the fruit from this tree
will be sent to me.
So
you like to eat this kind of small tangerines?
Actually, it's not me who likes it.
Here's the story.
A long time ago,
my brother once swallowed a Pearl of Fire for me.
He was suffering at the time
and had no appetite for anything.
But one day,
I saw him eat a whole Dan Tangerine,
so I was very happy.
Then I went out to look for it.
After I found an orchard,
I forced them
to cut down all the fruit trees in the orchard
and plant Dan Tangerines only.
And then?
Then my brother scolded me.
From then on, he mistakenly thought that I like to eat Dan Tangerine,
and even planted a Dan Tangerine tree in my house.
You should know
that it is not easy to grow this kind of tree
in the demon world.
He must have
put a lot of effort into
getting our Dan Tangerine tree
to grow and bear fruit.
You were weird too.
In that case,
why didn't you explain it to your brother?
Of course I can't give in
since he scolded me.
I'm different from you.
If my brother scolds me,
I will give in immediately,
and then act cute to him.
That way
he'll listen to me in everything.
How is your brother?
I heard something happened to Palace Chonghua today.
Exactly.
Even Liu Shao
was imprisoned in the furnace by Bai Feng.
But
fortunately your brother arrived in time
and saved her.
So she was safe at last.
My brother?
It turned out
that my brother was injured by the spirit fire in Immortal Palace,
so he was attacked by that eagle demon.
Luo Ge.
Liu Shao.
I will take revenge on you.
You are...
I am the one who once punished your people,
and the one who can save your people.
God of the Moonlight?
I'm Fu from Aquatic Demons.
Greetings, Supreme God.
I know that you have a lot of resentment.
So do I.
If you can lift the curse of my people,
I am willing to do everything
to eliminate all your resentment.
Good.
It just so happens that I want to borrow something from you
to facilitate my work tomorrow.
He actually absorbed 30% of my demon power.
But if he can really
bring chaos to Immortal Palace,
it will be worth it.
If you were just that mortal Lu Li,
and if only we could stay together forever
after we first met that day.
If I don't have the responsibility to protect all creatures in this world,
and if our spiritual power won't interfere with each other,
that would be great.
There is a barrier of fate
between us.
If we can be together,
I am willing to fight against the fate of the Three Realms.
But...
The one who would hurt you
is actually me.
How ridiculous.
The person I hurt
is the love of my life.
So I can only leave you.
I hated
and loved
this Immortal Palace.
Now we will separate
and forget about each other.
Who are you?
I am the complete you.
The Four Seasons Monument is still there,
all this is just my illusion.
Or should I say
illusions come from the heart?
Why don't you give up?
Why should I give up?
You cut off all your emotions
in order to become Immortal.
You met someone you like,
but you were afraid to express your love to her.
Then why do you still
want to be an Immortal?
I have been cultivating hard
for all beings
and the Three Realms.
My personal pursuits are nothing.
Cultivating hard?
If so,
what do you have in your hand?
What I can't escape, you can't escape either.
What I can't get, you can't get either.
What I have experienced,
you will also experience.
You will eventually become me.
No way.
What's the point of you cultivating hard to become an Immortal?
Even if you protect all living beings,
you'll lose yourself
and hurt
your loved ones.
This is...
Lu Sheng.
This is Soul-devouring Spell,
and I will plant it in your body.
If you are in love with Liu Shao,
you will trigger the spell to break out.
If you can't stop your love for Liu Shao,
this spell will make your blood flow backwards,
bring you extreme pain.
Soul-devouring Spell?
This is Lu Li's memory.
Impossible.
I really can't break
this Soul-devouring Spell.
It's just Soul-devouring Spell...
Why...
Luo Ge.
Xiyin Mountain is falling.
Something happened to Luo Ge.
What I have experienced,
you'll experience too.
You will eventually become me.
Brother.
Luo Ge!
What happened?
Are you okay?
Luo Ge.
Liu Shao,
listen to me.
This evil spirit is getting stronger and stronger.
I was almost affected by it today.
I have to do something.
If I continue to ignore the vibration
of Xiyin Mountain,
I am afraid that all living beings in the Three Realms will be destroyed.
How could this happen?
No.
It shouldn't be like this.
As long as I don't bother you...
This has nothing to do with you.
I wanted to keep Lu Li's cultivation,
but I deliberately cut off Lu Li's emotions.
Now,
I've been tormented by my heart demon.
Luo Ge.
Love will corrode the heart,
and emotion will corrode the bones.
It was all illusory,
but I couldn't get out of this predicament.
Then how can I be an Immortal?
Luo Ge.
Luo Ge!
Then let's just give up.
We can stop doing it anymore.
Let's go.
Let's go back, okay?
It's just that if this continues,
all beings in the Three Realms will be implicated by me.
Liu Shao,
just be yourself.
I have to face my responsibility
and go through the tribulation again.
Luo Ge!
Liu Shao.
Luo Ge.
God of the Moonlight.
How did you create this Soul-devouring Spell?
It forbids one to fall in love with another.
Luo Ge.
Luo Ge!
You have so much responsibility to take on.
This Soul-devouring Spell was given to you because of me.
I should be the one to take it.
Masters,
have something similar happened in the past?
Yes.
And it also caused chaos in Immortal Palace.
It will endanger the Three Realms.
How can we solve it?
It is said
that we can get Immortal back.
Or we can have another Immortal in Immortal Palace.
Greetings, Immortal Master.
What happened to Luo Ge this time
was his misfortune.
But if he can
get over his heart demon and come back,
he will definitely get stronger.
But when will he come back?
If he doesn't return,
who can solve the chaos in Xiyin Mountain?
If he's going to stay in the human world for another twenty years,
I'm afraid the Three Realms will become chaotic again.
Master Shang has been cultivating for a long time,
why not let him activate Xilun Formation,
so that he can become an Immortal immediately.
As long we have an Immortal here,
we can also solve many problems.
Xilun Formation is dangerous.
The person in the center of this formation will turn into stone at any moment.
We cannot activate it arbitrarily.
Report!
Master,
the cracks on the Four Seasons Monument have intensified,
and there is evil aura overflowing from the bottom of the monument.
Immortal Master, senior.
Masters.
Now is not the time to worry about other things.
It is important to unite everyone's strength
to seal this evil aura.
Okay.
Do you think I can't deal with you
if you go to the human world?
This little guy is really here.
Since you won't let me out,
I'll use the Son of the Demon King to collect divine spirit
to restore my strength.
I will make you pay
for sealing me for ten thousand years.
[Ao Hen's son, Ao Yin]
Luo Ge.
Where are you?
Why couldn't I find you
anywhere?
What?
[Marquis Wuyang's Mansion]
Brother?
Yes.
Has he been here?
No.
I know
that with the Moon Bell protecting you,
you'll be safe.
Luo Ge has never been here.
I will send men to find him.
Luo Ge.
I will find you.
No matter who you became this time,
I would definitely recognize you.
Wait for me.
The God of the Moonlight
is really amazing.
He only used 30% of my demon power
to make Luo Ge become like this.
Now Immortal Palace has been busy because of Four Seasons Monument.
Luo Ning.
What's wrong, Luo Ning?
Who bullied you?
Fu.
My brother has been missing for so long.
Could something really happen to him?
Don't worry.
Luo Ge is an Immortal.
He can solve any problem.
But he disappeared without a trace.
We also don't know his whereabouts
in the human world.
Immortal Palace would definitely send someone to find him.
No.
I'm going to find him myself.
You've never left here.
You have no idea of the dangers of the human world.
If your brother knew,
he would definitely not let you leave.
What if something happened to your brother?
I...
Luo Ning.
I'll go with you.
Yurong.
Thank you for your hard work today.
It's not a big deal.
It's just that we can't last too long
if we take turns to fix it like this.
If Luo Ge doesn't come back,
the situation
will get worse.
If Ge doesn't come back,
Immortal Palace
will still keep falling,
and the Four Seasons Monument will keep breaking.
Then we won't be able
to stop this demon from coming out.
Below Xiyin Mountain is the human world,
once it sinks,
the entire human world will be affected.
Besides,
the demon under the monument
once killed so many lives in the Three Realms ten thousand years ago.
Now there is not even someone to stop him.
Once he comes out,
he will definitely kill many lives again.
When Luo Ge first set this formation,
he made seven talisman pearls in Liu Shao's body.
Four were used up at the time,
and she still has three in her body now.
It should buy us some time
if we use magic to get them out.
But didn't Liu Shao
go to the human world with Luo Ge?
Before Liu Shao left,
I had left a mark on her.
We should be able to find her.
Take my fan. This suits you very well.
You're still here?
Hong.
Take mine.
There's a fool selling pearls by the Moon River.
It's interesting.
Let's go. I'll take you there.
Over there.
Moon River?
Could it be...
♫I ask the cloud and the flower♫
♫How I can stop missing you♫
♫I walk through the time♫
♫Whether we can forever♫
♫Love each other like now and carve this between our eyebrows♫
♫A white horse came and became a poem♫
♫Memory is beautiful and I am still loving you♫
♫In the vast blue sky, I prefer to pursue the moon♫
Why are you here?
We can catch the moon in the Moon River.
♫Do you know it?♫
Are you going or not?
♫Thousands of lights made it like a day♫
Is this the moon you mentioned?
Of course not.
Close your eyes.
♫It is like my heart where you are still there♫
Ready?
♫I am waiting. The moon is above the willow branch♫
How much
is this bracelet?
Miss.
♫I only want to hold your hands and count beans of love♫
This bracelet is unusual.
This bead
♫I am guarding you. A turning around♫
was raised by the lake demons
who gouged out one of their own eyes
and placed it in a golden clam for their own children.
♫Exchanges staying together forever♫
It will definitely help you ward off demons
and suppress evils.
♫The love is as before♫
How much is it?
It's not expensive.
One thousand taels.
You're talking nonsense.
Are you kidding?
You are making up stories to lie.
Yes.
Mr. Lu, let's go.
Mr. Shao, let's go.
I'm not lying.
You have no idea what you are missing.
Why do I feel
that someone will definitely buy it?
It's not worth one thousand taels at all.
♫Do you know it?♫
Five thousand taels.
♫Thousands of lights made it like a day♫
I'll have it.
♫It is like my heart where you are still there♫
♫I am waiting. The moon is above the willow branch♫
♫I only want to hold your hands and count beans of love♫
Don't let that lake demon
gouge out the other eye
♫I am guarding you. A turning around♫
to keep his child safe for the winter.
Miss.
♫Exchanges staying together forever♫
The one I've been waiting for
♫The love is as before♫
is you.